sealedair.com 2018-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Sealed Air

Updated: July 13, 2017

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Sealed Air Corporation  (the “ **Company** ”) respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) applies to Personal Information (as defined below) we collect on sealedair.com and other Company websites that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the " **Site(s)** "). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, made subject to and is governed by, that certain Web Site Terms of Use (“ **Terms** ”) by and between the Company and you (“ **you** ”, “ **your** ”). Capitalized terms used, but not defined in this Privacy Policy, have the meanings given to them in the Terms.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect on the Site(s), how we may use that information, with whom we may share it and what we do to protect it. We also tell you how you can reach us to ask us to update your preferences regarding how we communicate with you or answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not address use and disclosure of your information by our business partners who may offer services through our Site(s) or link to our Site(s).  These entities have their own policies describing their practices.  

**Information We Collect**

When you visit the Site(s), you may provide (and we may collect) information such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number, payment account information (such as credit card information), demographic information or other personal information (hereinafter “ **Personal Information** ”) when using the Site(s), such as when you register for an account, and when you create content submissions or when you interact with other users of the Site(s), such as through features such as posting feedback.  Below is a brief, general description of the types of information we collect through the Site(s):

Information Through Devices: Company’s suite of smart devices, applications and digital tracking solutions (e.g., IntelliDish, IntelliCare, IntelliTrail, IntelliTrak, IntelliConsult) also collect various forms of non-Personal Information, such as device usage data, location data, and business intelligence data. To the extent that any mobile device of yours utilizes one of our applications, we may collect locational data relating to such device(s), provided you have agreed to such processing. Such locational data may be able to be matched up with other data to derive Personal Information. **,**

Sensitive Personal Information:  Provided you have agreed to the processing of such information, we may also collect information that reveals race, ethnic origin, sexual orientation, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or that concerns an individual’s health or workplace habits. Such information is sometimes referred to as “Sensitive Personal Information”.

If you use an external social network (for example, your Facebook, Google+, or Linkedin account) to log in to the Site(s) or to interact with the Company in another way, we may collect your name and other details from your social network and account. For example, on our careers pages, you can choose to use your social network account to log in or to provide us (via our service provider iCIMS) with a dynamic resume that will be automatically updated over time as you update your social network account. (You can stop any ongoing sharing of data by using your social network's account settings).

Cookies

When you visit our Site(s), we and third parties may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons. Cookies are small files that websites and email servers place and access on your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or device or to store information or settings in your device. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict, disable or delete certain cookies. Please note, however, that without certain cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site(s).  For example, we may use certain essential cookies that are set when you enter some of our Site(s) to assist with navigation during your visit or when you complete certain forms.  Blocking these cookies or deleting them earlier than their normal expiration date may cause problems.

Automatically Collected Information

Our web servers may log information such as your device and operating system type, browser type, domain, device ID, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. The web server logs also may record information such as the address of the web page that referred you to our Site(s) and the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet.

To control which web servers place and access cookies and collect information by automated means, we may place tags on our Web pages called "web beacons", which are small files that allow us to understand the actions of visitors to our Site(s).  We may use similar technology in email we send, which may enable the placing or accessing of cookies, and also enable us to know if you received the email, if the email was opened and if you clicked on any links in the email.

In addition, we collect information you provide to us when you perform site searches, place orders or renew services, edit information in your profile or regarding the Products you use, communicate with us by phone, e-mail, text services, or otherwise; participate in blogs, discussion boards or community postings.

Third Party Data Collection.

We use third-party web analytics services on our Site(s), such as those of Google Analytics. These service providers use cookies and web beacons or other technology to help us analyze how users use the Site(s). The information collected by such technology (including, where applicable, your IP address) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to facilitate the evaluation of your use of the Site(s).

Third parties may collect Personal Information about your online activities over time and across different Site(s) when you use our Site(s). For example, third-party providers of certain embedded content and tools on our Site(s) (such as an embedded Twitter or Facebook feed, or an embedded blog commenting system from DISQUS, or any social network that you can use to log in to our Site(s) or to submit information to our Site(s)) may collect Personal Information directly from you in connection with your interaction with such content and tools.

Data about your activities on our Site(s) may be collected for use in providing advertising tailored to your individual interests on other websites and online services. You may choose whether to have your information collected for that purpose. We participate in advertising services administered by third parties.  The ad services may track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of the automated technologies described above, and they may use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests and/or based on prior visits to our Site(s).  We and third-party vendors may use first-party cookies and third-party cookies alone or together, as well as other automated means and the data collected through such means and from other sources (i) to inform, optimize, and serve ads (involving ads based on past visits to our Site(s)), and (ii) to report on our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services (including how they are related to visits to our Site(s)).  

We will not collect more Personal Information than is reasonably necessary or relevant to enable you to fully enjoy the use of our Site(s) and associated features, and for the provision of the Products, other services, or support.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

We may use the information we obtain about you when you visit the Site(s) for various purposes, including to:

  * Verify your identity; 
  * Process, evaluate, and respond to your requests, inquiries, and applications; 
  * Create, administer, and communicate with you about your accounts; 
  * Contact you with marketing communications, if you have given your consent; 
  * Process data to enable us to provide the Products and services that you and/or your company have purchased or licensed from the Company;
  * Contact you as necessary to enforce the Terms;
  * Give you access to your user profile and Site history;
  * To aggregate and remove personally identifiable aspects of such data in order to perform data analytics services provided you have given your consent or processing is allowed by law;
  * Operate, evaluate, and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; performing market research and data analytics; determining and managing the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing; analyzing and customizing our products, services, Site(s) and communications; administering our Site(s); and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation, and collection activities provided you have given your consent or processing is allowed by law.);
  * Process your employment application and contact you regarding possible employment based on information you submit through the Site(s);
  * Protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure and quality; 
  * Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies and terms, such as our Terms;
  * To monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed
  * To comply with and fulfill the obligations under any commercial agreement we have with you or the entity with which you are employed or contracted;

We retain Personal Information only for so long as it is necessary or relevant to fulfill the above mentioned purposes or comply with applicable law, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems or assist with investigations. After it is no longer necessary for us to retain Personal Information, we dispose of it in accordance with our data retention and disposal policies.

**Data Transfers**

_Transfers to Third Party Suppliers_

Company may engage in transfers of Personal Information collected from you to third-party service providers that Company uses to support the provision of the Products and other content and services.  As allowed by applicable law, Company may disclose automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties, to assist such parties in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality available through the Company. _  _Generally, these disclosures are made under terms comparable to this Privacy Policy, and the recipients are limited to using the information the purpose for which it was provided.

As allowed by applicable law, we may also share certain Personal Information among our affiliates and joint marketing partners for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  We may provide Personal Information to our authorized distributors for the purpose of contacting you for follow-up regarding your requests or for keeping you informed of new activities. 

Company may use third party payment processing services, and your Personal Information may be disclosed to such providers in connection with processing your payment of fees and other transactions you initiate on the Site(s).

The Company will only transfer such information to third parties that contractually agree to protect such data in a manner that is no less restrictive than Company’s own standards for the protection of its own Personal Information.

_Transfers outside of Geographic Point of Collection_.

We may transfer the Personal Information we collect about you to locations in the United States or other countries that differ from the one in which the information originally was collected.  Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information.  When we transfer your information internationally, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with applicable law.

If your data is collected from the EU, you will have the right to opt-in to the use and transfer of such information as set forth below.  You will also have the right to opt-out of such use at any time during the Term subsequent to an initial ‘opt in’ by changing your preferences or by writing to us.  Our contact information is below.

_Transfers Required by Law_.

Subject to applicable law, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process, such as a subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government entities, such as law enforcement authorities; (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical, financial or other harm, injury or loss; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.  

**Your Choices**

If you would like to update or modify your information or subscription preferences, you may contact us as described in the “Contact Us” section below.  On certain Site(s), you may be able to make these choices directly by logging into your account.  You also may unsubscribe from any of our promotional emails by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in any promotional email you receive from us. Changes made to your profile will be effective once saved into our systems in accordance with our standard procedures for implementing user questions regarding your Personal Information.

Depending on the data protection law of your country, you may have a legal right to obtain access to Personal Information we maintain about you.  In addition, if you believe the Personal Information is inaccurate, you may have the legal right to request that we correct or amend the information.  To make these requests, or to object to our processing of your Personal Information or withdraw consent to such processing (rights provided by the laws of certain countries), you may contact us as described in the Contact Us section below.

_Opt-In (for Sensitive Personal Information)_

As stated above, we may collect Sensitive Personal Information if you provide your consent. If you wish to opt-in to the collection and use of Sensitive Personal Information by us to provide services to you, which may include the transfer of such Sensitive Personal Information to third parties, then you may opt-in to such uses by checking the ‘opt-in’ box in your user preferences, or through this opt-in form using the selected drop boxes. If none of the available options meets your requirements, or you have other questions, please contact us directly.

_Opt-Out (for third party transfers)_

We disclose Personal Information to our third party partners as described in the section Data Transfer. If you wish to limit or restrict the disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties, you may opt-out of such third party disclosures by changing your preferences in your profile or sending us a notice via email or through this opt-out request form.  If you have previously granted an ‘opt-in’ for certain collection and use practices with respect to Personal Information, you may issue a subsequent ‘opt-out’ by changing your preferences in your profile or sending us a notice via email. Our contact information is below.

**How We Protect Personal Information**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but despite our efforts, we cannot promise that that our security program will always eliminate all possible security risks, and our liability is limited as set forth in the Terms.  

Company uses commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard and protect the security of all data, inclusive of any Personal Information collected by the Company from you through the Site(s).  Company maintains certain administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect the security of the Personal Information we collect on the Site(s). Personal Information and other data are stored in hosted and secured environments which utilize accepted industry standards for data security. Company uses commercially reasonable efforts to partner with third party service providers that meet accepted industry standards to support the collection, storage, hosting, processing and retention of data, inclusive of Personal Information.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Company cannot, however, ensure, warrant or guarantee that the information collected by the Company will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by system malfunction or circumvention of our safeguards.

It is also important for you to comply with the access controls (e.g., username/password management) and other applicable provisions of the Terms to protect against unauthorized access to your account and to the devices you use to access the Site(s).

**Links to Other Third Party Websites; Third Party Activity**

Our Site(s) may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. Those websites may be operated by companies not affiliated with. Linked websites may have their own privacy policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of any websites that are not affiliated with us, any use of those websites, or the privacy practices of those websites.

**Complaints**  

Should you have any complaints regarding the use of Personal Information by us, you contact us below.

**Dispute Resolution**

Disputes will be governed in accordance with the Terms.

**Human Resources Data**

Company may collect Personal information relating to applications for employment with the Company through our careers page, such as your résumé, and other information relevant to specific jobs advertised on our Site(s). Such Personal Information will be subject to the Terms hereof. You will be required to opt-in for the submission of any such Personal Information submitted through our careers page.

**Mergers, Acquisitions & Reorganizations**

In the event that all or a portion of Company or its assets are acquired by, reorganized or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from users in connection with such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.  In such an event, we will require any such buyer or third party to agree to treat your Site(s) in a manner that is no less restrictive than set forth in this Privacy Policy or the Terms.

**Order of Priority**

This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Use, including, without limitation, all disclaimers and limitations of liability set forth therein. In the event of any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the Terms, the Terms shall control.

**Updates to Our Privacy Policy**

The Company may, in its sole discretion, update this Privacy Policy periodically without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our Personal Information practices or with respect to applicable laws. We will post the updated version on our Site(s) and indicate at the top when it was last updated.

Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Privacy Policy.  In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder we will make commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of the change.  For example, we may send a message to your email address, if we have one on file, or generate a pop-up or similar notifications when you access the Site(s) for the first time after such material changes are made.  Our amended Privacy Policy will automatically take effect upon the date that an update is published, except that (a) we will not, without your consent, use your previously collected Personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that information, and (b) if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy, you may terminate your account ceasing use of the Site(s).  Your continued use of the Site(s) after the revised or updated Privacy Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the then-current version of the Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us as indicated below:

Sealed Air  
Attn: Executive Director, Digital & Social Marketing  
2415 Cascade Pointe Blvd.  
Charlotte, NC 28208
